Boss! Boss!
- What is that?
- Hey, you masked bastard.
Now you're dead meat.
Hey, attack him!
Attack him, quickly!
Hey, hurry up!
What the hell?
This bastard. Hey, hey, get up.
Hey, you bastard! Get over here!
Huh? Come on!
Hey, he's alive. Damn it.
The bathroom.
Hey, there's big trouble in the bathroom.
- Get to the bathroom, now!
- You bastard!
Kang-sik!
Boss.
Hey!
Go!
Hey, lock the door!
You!
In-gu!
You hear that?
It means you're a dead man.
Damn it.
- What?
- What the?
- Turn on the lights!
- What the hell?
- Where did he go?
- Hey, find him, quick!
Find him, now!
ORAN CHINESE RESTAURANT
EPISODE 4
Where have you been?
You weren't answering your phone.
Ho-myeong.
It's an emergency, so be quiet...
What happened to your face? Are you hurt?
I just fell off my motorcycle.
- I need some rest.
- Good grief.
I need to talk to you.
You two can head home first.
All right, then. You two wrap
things up and come along.
- Okay, let's go.
- Hold on.
We should hear what happened too.
We need to go now.
It's time to go.
Let's go.
Talk to me.
You haven't answered your phone all day.
So why are you crawling in now,
looking like that?
I was out on a delivery...
I crashed my bike, and when I came to,
it was already this late.
Where?
Mr. Kim said he drove
all around the neighborhood
and didn't see you.
Let's talk about it later.
Tell me before you go.
- Can't you see I'm hurt?
- Exactly.
Where were you
and what were you doing to get so hurt...
that you didn't go pick up Ji-woo?
Don't tell me...
you just remembered now?
Are you out of your mind? Ji-woo...
That six-year-old boy...
Because you never showed up
he walked home by himself for 30 minutes.
Is Ji-woo okay?
And that makes it okay?
What if on his way home alone...
he'd gotten into an accident?
What would you have done
if he'd gotten lost?
I'm sorry.
You're sorry?
For what?
Why are you always like this, huh?
Why can't you just tell me straight?
You're just going to clam up like that?
7 YEARS AGO
Seong-won, I...
I'm getting married.
O-ran's... pregnant.
Hey, you idiot!
How could you be so careless?
Is this really the time
for you to get married?
- What about the operation?
- Getting married won't change anything.
My revenge on Han Gyeong-wook,
finding Bulgae...
everything will proceed without a hitch.
You think it's as easy as it sounds?
What are you going to do when the time
comes to choose between them?
Why are you being so negative?
I can do both.
Jeez, Ho-myeong.
Do you know why I never got married?
I thought it was because you couldn't.
I've also spent my life
thinking a family would just get
in the way of the operation.
But, no.
The moment Oran told me about the baby,
I realized something.
That for my family...
there's nothing I wouldn't do.
Hey, President Yoo.
Are you okay?
You feeling all right?
How did you know I was here?
Come on. Of course I had to visit.
A coworker got hurt.
But...
this isn't a private room.
Could you move aside?
Who the hell are you
to tell a patient to move?
- Hey!
- Damn it.
Everyone, get out.
Yes, Boss.
All of you, get out.
- Yes, sir.
Out, out, out, out.
You're more hurt than I thought.
That son of a bitch.
I heard it was just one guy
who did all this.
Is this for real?
The almighty Ingu Sect?
Stay out of what happens on my turf.
No way.
I'd love to stay out of it.
But you know how it is.
The day after tomorrow,
I have to report to Chief Han
on the Yeongseon Island project.
All right, the security room incident,
that's number one. And...
this one is number two.
With all this trouble
happening with Heaven Capital
I'm not quite sure what stance to take.
It's putting me in a tough spot.
You know?
Hey, Chairman Do.
You think I can't clean up
a mess like this?
Watch your mouth.
Keep running your mouth like that...
and you'll end up dead.
I know, I know.
I know exactly
what you're capable of, President Yoo.
That's why we're in the same boat.
As long as this business goes smoothly
I have no problem.
No problem.
Oh.
Vitamins.
Please.
Make sure you take these vitamins
and get well soon.
Get better.
Goodbye.
We'll talk business next time.
Bye.
See you.
Why...
What is it, boss?
- What is it?
- Go bring me that Masked Bastard.
Boss, I...
How am I supposed to find him
when we don't know who he is?
Hey, you moron! Isn't it obvious?
The guy who took down
our Ingu Sect all by himself
who else holds a grudge against us?
Who else could it be
but that Martial Arts Master
we beat up and took his house deed from?
But his fighting style...
it felt different
from the masked guy's. Right?
- Yeah.
- Forget his damn fighting style
and just go get him!
We'll know...
- We'll get him
- When we beat it out of him! Damn it!
I'll get him.
Damn it.
SEOUL METROPOLITAN POLICE AGENCY
Hey.
- Did you look into what I asked?
- Yes.
The most important part you need to see
is on page three.
This is the Hwasan Sect's
organizational chart from ten years ago.
At the time, the boss, Hwang Hwa-san
was charged with soliciting
the murder of Kwon Soon-bok
and after he received a life sentence,
the sect fell apart.
The second-in-command, Gang Beom-ryong
suddenly disappeared without a trace.
So he's missing?
It's hard to say.
In any case, there's no record
of any activity after that.
And so, naturally
the number three, Yoo In-gu
ended up taking over
the entire Hwasan Sect.
He even changed the gang's name from the
Hwasan Sect
to the Ingu Sect
and expanded their influence.
Yoo In-gu.
Have his whereabouts been confirmed?
Yes. It's on the last page.
It's called Heaven Capital
on Yeongseon Island
located inside Heaven Casino.
His most recent move was registering it
as a private lending company.
Wait a minute.
Did you say Yeongseon Island?
Yes. Is there a problem?
YEONGSEON ISLAND
Yeongseon Island.
So...
you came back empty-handed?
See? This is why I told you
not to go off on your own.
By the way,
the jerky factory seemed suspicious.
- I thought we should hit it...
- Stop it!
Don't you dare go there alone.
Why not?
I can handle it.
Ho-myeong.
You're not the man you used to be.
You need to face reality.
If you get hurt,
what will you tell your family?
You know that Prosecutor Gang I mentioned?
I think we're just about to entangle her.
So until then, just lay low
and go score some points with your wife.
What's with the sudden advice?
It's not like you're a marriage counselor.
I just hate seeing you
so down in the dumps.
Didn't you say you could handle both?
So just do that and lay low.
And absolutely no acting
on your own. Got it?
I'm hanging up.
Did you find anything?
Yes.
The masked assailant...
It seems President Yoo's men
are desperately looking for him.
The rumor is he's the one who caused
the problem in the security office.
In any case,
he's clearly not your average guy.
He single-handedly
wiped out the Ingu Sect.
Of course he's not average.
Follow up on that
in more detail.
- Understood.
- Also.
Did you look into that jerky business
I mentioned?
They're disguising drugs from China
as beef jerky and distributing them.
Besides our casino
they have a pretty solid
distribution network set up nationwide.
Goodness... Well, I'll be.
Let's see.
The monthly volume is...
REPORT ON YOO IN-GU
AND COMPANY'S DRUG TRAFFICKING
ESTIMATED MONTHLY DISTRIBUTION VOLUME
50KG
Fifty kilograms.
Wow. And the revenue...
Ten, one hundred thousand,
one million, ten million...
Fifteen billion won.
Man, this Yoo In-gu.
He's got a better head
for business than I thought.
To think he built such a cash cow.
What should we do?
This jerky business...
There could be some serious synergy
if we link it to our casino.
If we passed it around the VIP rooms
it could be very lucrative.
This...
There's no reason not to do it, is there?
Let's see.
So all we have to do
is get rid of President Yoo
and we'll be all set.
But making an open move...
is a bit risky.
Do you have a plan?
The enemy's gates down.
but only from the inside.
What does that mean?
The gates of an enemy's fortress
can only be opened from the inside.
Let's find a gatekeeper
who'll throw the gates
wide open for us.
Damn it.
Hey, you find anything?
Boss.
Looks like he already took off.
Yeah, it sure looks like it. Damn it.
Where the hell
are we supposed to find him?
Hey, Boss!
- Look at this.
- What is it?
Remember Martial Arts Master?
He said he worked at an office, didn't he?
I'm just an ordinary office worker.
Just... an office worker.
Well, look at the brains on this one.
Hey, pull up the address for this company.
- Got it?
- Right away, sir.
Let's move. Come on, boys, let's go!
- Yes, sir!
Buying this is our little
secret from Mom, okay?
I know.
You keep it a secret too, Dad.
I'm sorry about yesterday.
I made you walk home by yourself.
But, Dad...
Why didn't you come yesterday?
Did you have too many deliveries?
Well...
You know your favorite, Masked Racer?
He has to go right away
when he gets a call, right?
Well, Dad also
got called to action yesterday, too.
You got called to fight bad guys, too?
Whoa, that's so cool.
This is a secret from Mom, too.
Why?
You should've told Mom
you were on a mission.
Mom's really angry.
- Really?
- Grandpa said
that she won't get over it
easily this time.
Dad, I asked I-seo
and she said there's a way
to calm Mom down.
What is it?
No matter how mad she gets
if you compliment her, give her a gift
and take her on a date,
she'll get over it.
- A date?
- Dad.
Do you see that?
MASKED RACER'S GREAT ADVENTURE
Oh, my back.
Jeez, where did that guy go now?
Yeongseon Food?
YEONGSEON FOOD
- Hey, get him!
- Get him!
- What do you think you're doing?
- Get in there!
Whoa, hold on there! Just a second.
Hey, it's all right. Come on.
- Come over here.
- Me?
It's all right.
It's fine.
Come here.
- I just want to ask you something, okay?
- Okay...
That guy, Bong Je-sun, works here, right?
Where might that punk be?
PAYSTUB
MANAGER BONG JE-SUN
Manager Bong?
Yeah, Manager Bong.
So where is he? You don't know?
He should be in the factory
on the second floor right now.
Second floor factory? Where is it?
Over there.
Hey, it's the second floor!
Let's go, hurry!
Yes, sir, yes!
Hey! Second floor.
Move it!
Manager Bong!
Manager Bong! What are you doing here?
People were saying
the bathroom was too dirty.
That's not the problem!
There are gangsters outside. Gangsters!
The gangsters are here to get you!
Nam-il.
Nam-il, get up.
What? Uncle, are you off work already?
Gangsters are here! Get up, quick!
Gangsters...
Manager Bong, what are you doing?
Hey, what's this?
I'm sorry, sir. I...
- I'll explain later. I'm sorry.
- Hey! What do you mean, later?
Sir, I'll explain later.
Hey!
Hey! Get him!
Get in, quick!
- That way!
- Got it.
Hey, stop right there!
Hey! There's the bastard!
Get him! Hey, hurry up!
Go, get him!
That hurts!
Get him!
Hey, stop!
Wait, hold on.
Hey, what's going on?
Damn it!
Oh no!
Bensun! No.
My Bensun!
How many times do I have to tell you?
I'll need to see your ID.
I told you, I crossed on yellow.
- Are you blind?
- Your ID, please.
Gosh, seriously.
Here you go.
What a stuck-up bitch.
- What the!
- You startled me.
Oh, I'm sorry. I just...
you were standing out here in the rain.
Oh, it was you.
You have to give out tickets
even in weather like this?
Yeah, pretty much.
Here, please take this.
- What about you?
- The bus drops me off
right in front of my convenience store.
You'll catch a cold if you stand
in the rain for too long.
- That's my bus. I've gotta go.
- Oh, wait!
Hey, wait a minute! Stop, stop!
Hey! Sir, let me get on!
Stop!
Sir, stop! Come on.
I said stop! Please, stop!
Get in. It's on my way.
I'll give you a ride.
No, it's okay, really.
It feels nice and cool. I'm fine.
You know the buses here
only run once an hour, right?
Get in.
But I'm completely soaked.
You're the one who said
you'll catch a cold standing in the rain.
It's fine.
So...
You're a fan of Chow Yun Fat, aren't you?
Whoa! How did you know that?
You popped up
on my "Friends You May Know" list.
Your PFP is Chow Yun Fat, right?
I'm a big fan of his too,
so I just thought I'd mention it.
Wow, really? No way, I had no idea.
Sorry, what's a "PFP"?
Profile picture.
Oh, the picture.
Anyway, A Better Tomorrow...
I remember watching that on VHS
when I was a kid. I loved it.
Oh, right.
A Better Tomorrow on VHS.
It's a true masterpiece. You know...
In that case,
you know A Better Tomorrow...
is being rereleased
for its 40th anniversary, right?
Of course.
Well, A Better Tomorrow is a movie that...
is too much of a masterpiece
to be wasted on a small screen.
So maybe, since this
opportunity came up...
how about seeing it in a theater?
Oh...
I'd love to, but...
I'm not a big fan
of going to the movies by myself
and I don't really have anyone to go with.
Oh, I see.
Oh, man. What to do?
Well, in that case...
at the movie theater...
How about doing a
"going to the movies alone" challenge?
You know those "eating alone" challenges?
It's been popular since the pandemic.
- By myself?
- A lot of the younger crowd does it.
By myself... Sure, I guess.
- A challenge?
- A challenge. Be cool about it.
Yeah, why not?
JUMBO24
CONVENIENCE STORE
Thank... Thank you.
Thanks for the ride.
You should get going. You must be busy.
Okay.
- Excuse me, sir.
- Yes?
A Better Tomorrow.
When are you going to see it?
It comes out the day after tomorrow
- so I'm going on opening day.
- Really?
- Yes.
- I happen to be
off the day after tomorrow.
Oh, really?
Oh, do you guys work two shifts or three?
The police, I mean.
- Do you want to go together?
- Go where?
To the movies.
A Better Tomorrow.
I'm asking you to go see it with me.
- You don't want to?
- No.
I'd love to.
Okay, I'll contact you about the time.
Okay.
- I'll be in touch.
- Okay.
It doesn't hurt.
- Come on.
- Yes, boss.
Oh, are you all right? Boss, really...
I have all my men searching for him.
If you could just give me
a little more time...
Hey, you son of a bitch.
The deal our entire organization's future
depends on is the day after tomorrow
and you want more time?
If that Martial Arts Master shows up
and ruins the whole thing
how can we go through with the deal
when we don't even know
what that bastard is after?
Boss, please.
Wouldn't it be better
to just postpone the deal?
You know how big the down payment is,
and you're still spouting that nonsense?
If the deal falls through
and we end up with nothing
- are you going to take responsibility?
- I'm sorry, sir.
The deal is happening
no matter what. Got it?
Before then, you catch that
Martial Arts Master and drag him to me.
- Yes, sir.
- Drag him here!
- Bring him to me!
- Yes, boss!
Let's go.
Damn, that hurts like hell.
How long do I have to take this beating?
Hey, Mr. Golden Boy.
Oh, yes, Chairman. Hello.
What's up, man?
Why the long face?
Something wrong?
Oh, it's nothing.
Oh, come on.
Don't be like that.
How about you and I...
go for a drive in my supercar?
With... with me?
Yes. It's for you.
Come on.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Just think of us as colleagues
and let's be comfortable, okay?
Here, have some coffee.
Yeah, relax.
Must be tough working
under President Yoo, huh?
No, not at all.
Oh, come on.
But for all the hard work you do
it seems you're not treated very well.
Your face is all banged up.
I mean, if it were me,
for a great ace like our Mr. Geum
I could make a much better offer.
I have no intention of betraying my boss.
Oh, I shouldn't have said that.
Hey, hey, hey.
Here, wipe the side
of your mouth. The coffee.
I'm not trying to talk about something
as serious as betrayal. It's just...
I wanted to chat with Mr. Geum
about the struggles at work.
For example
like the story
of the civilian who recently
laid waste to Heaven Capital.
Or what President Yoo
is secretly working on.
Interesting topics
like his jerky business.
Okay?
Chairman, how did you...
Come on.
There's no secret, man.
Sorry?
What... What did you say?
I mean, there are no secrets.
There are no secrets...
CASHIER'S CHECK 10,000,000 WON
The story our Mr. Geum told me today
how should I put it...
was so very moving.
- Right.
- Let's...
see each other again.
- What do you want?
- It's a gift from the Chairman.
A gift?
Chairman, thank you.
Oh, hello.
Welcome.
You must be coming
from the campaign trail.
You're a little late today, aren't you?
Yes, I suppose I am.
Can I get a special
and a bottle of soju, please?
Coming right up.
Yes, goodness.
Jeez.
Assemblyman Han, what are you doing here?
I heard rumors that this is the spot
Candidate Kim frequents every day
so I came to see for myself.
Am I making you uncomfortable?
No, no, not at all.
- Please, have a seat.
- Thank you.
The gukbap here is out of this world.
You should try it.
Here.
Let me pour you a drink.
- Ah, thank you.
- Here.
Let me.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I've been campaigning,
which isn't something I'm cut out for.
When I was on my first campaign trail
I shook so many hands
that my hands were covered in blisters.
Oh, really?
Shaking hands all day
until my arm felt like it would fall off
smiling until my face cramped up
and giving speeches
until my voice was hoarse
I couldn't help
but feel a sense of regret.
"Did I really run for office
just for this?"
How about you, Candidate Kim?
Running in this election
don't you regret it?
For someone who has spent
their entire life as an educator
playing the part of a politician
that doesn't suit you
must be incredibly difficult.
What if...
the things you want to accomplish
could be achieved
without you becoming mayor?
Would you still continue
with the election?
What are you trying to say?
YEONGSEON ISLAND ORPHANAGE
SUPPORT PROJECT PROPOSAL
COMMUNITY NETWORK, DEVELOPMENT AND
MANAGEMENT OF LOCAL RESOURCES...
If you withdraw from the race...
the orphanage on Yeongseon Island
that you care so deeply about...
the children there will also benefit.
I hear their donations are so meager
they can't even fix
the heating and cooling.
But we could easily
build them a new building.
Besides housing, we're also considering
a plan for scholarships.
To allow the children to pursue the
education they want
we are looking into ways
to provide support.
I'm sorry
but I'm going to pretend this
conversation never happened.
I can't support the children
with money from a questionable source.
Source?
Money is money.
Even if you pour
your entire salary into it
and volunteer every day...
do you think you could accomplish
even one thing on this plan?
You said you'd make Yeongseon Island
a place for children.
Were those all just empty words?
You asked me
if I regretted running for office.
Yes.
It's a struggle every day.
Every day, I want to run away.
For someone like me
who's only ever been a teacher
politics doesn't seem to be my calling.
But...
what's even scarier...
is the thought of Assemblyman Han
becoming mayor
ruining the island
and the children's futures
and me just turning a blind eye to it.
It seems this will be the last drink...
we'll have together.
Then order anything you'd like.
Since it's our last
it's on me.
That's all right.
CASHIER'S CHECK 100,000 WON
I've had more than enough.
Well, then.
YEONGSEON ISLAND ORPHANAGE
SUPPORT PROJECT PROPOSAL
Hey, Joong-gi.
It looks like I'll have to go do
some volunteer work at the orphanage soon.
If I go to Yeongseon Island now
it'll mess up the whole plan.
What are you talking about, Boss?
Some prosecutor came for a visit.
At first, I didn't know
what to make of it.
Who knew she'd be some hard-ass
so fixated on that case?
Beom-ryong.
You need to go meet this Prosecutor Gang
right away.
Wait, are you telling me
to help a prosecutor?
You think I enjoy working
with some low-life prosecutor?
Hey, but if it means
I can clear my name
and take down
that traitor bastard Yoo In-gu
I suppose I can learn to love my enemy.
I've already laid out the bait
so Prosecutor Gang
is sure to approach Yoo In-gu.
I need you to be proactive
and help her.
And start wrapping up your business.
My... my business?
But this could be our last chance.
We have to risk our lives and go all in.
We have to start gathering the boys
and supporting this Prosecutor Gang.
Do you think you'll have time
to run a business?
Why?
Is something holding you back?
MASKED RACER LIVE ACTION PLAY
MASKED RACER'S GREAT ADVENTURE
- What's this?
- You know...
Ji-woo loves Masked Racer.
They're putting on a show
at the Arts Center.
What about the dinner service tomorrow?
After Ji-woo was born
we've been so busy,
we haven't had a proper outing.
Let the three of us go,
get some fresh air for a change.
Just go.
Is it going to kill us to close
for a day or two?
We can just close after the lunch service.
Dad, even if we close
for one service, our sales...
Forget about the sales!
Do I have to walk on eggshells
running this place
wondering if you two are fighting?
Please, just go out and settle it already
one way or another.
Dad, it's not like
I was making things tense.
All right, fine. We're going, okay?
This is Ji-woo's favorite.
Assemblyman Han, step down!
- Step down! Step down!
Chairman Do, step down!
- Step down!
Oh, this is going to get ugly.
Yes, this is Gang Yeong-ae.
Going into the hotel right now...
I suggest you think twice about it.
Who are you, really?
Are you stalking me?
I'm not stalking you.
I'm trying to warn you. It's dangerous.
Okay, so who are you
to keep giving me these warnings?
- What, are we in a spy movie?
- Prosecutor Gang.
I helped you lose the detective
that was tailing you.
Don't you remember?
- Just trust me.
- Okay.
If you really want me to trust you,
come down to the prosecutor's office.
I'll run a nice, thorough
background check on you
and if you check out,
then I'll believe you.
Go home now.
Right.
I'll think about it while I eat.
You can eat at a time like this?
Manager Lee, you're here.
- Want an egg?
- No, I'm fine.
I brought as much of the stuff
the boss told me to throw out as I could.
This is all you could grab?
You could've tried harder.
Thanks. Thank you.
When I go back to work
I'll cover all your tasks. Thank you.
I don't think that's going to happen.
Manager Bong.
Your employment was terminated,
effective today.
No. I...
Fired? But why?
You really don't know?
You constantly missed work
you were secretly living at the office
and you brought thugs
who wrecked the boss's car.
The boss was about to
call the police on you
for trespassing and a hit-and-run.
I barely convinced him
not to press charges
by agreeing to fire you
and deduct it from your severance.
So...
So, try not to feel like
this is too unfair.
What? Uncle, you got fired?
So are we completely broke now? Huh?
Do you have anywhere to go?
Does it look like it?
There are thugs outside looking for us.
Manager Bong.
Do you just need a place
that provides room and board?
I mean, I know a job
that provides room and board
that I could introduce you to.
But I'm not sure if you'd be good at it...
I'll do it. Yeah, I'll definitely do it.
I'll be great at it, no matter what.
Cleaning, washing cars?
What is it?
D-DAY
Excuse me.
How can I help you?
I'm Prosecutor Gang Yeong-ae
from Imcheon District Prosecutors' Office.
I'm here to see the president...
Oh, my.
You're Mr. Yoo In-gu, aren't you?
A prosecutor, visiting a clean
and legitimate business like ours...
what could possibly bring you here?
Well, I...
I'm currently investigating a case.
And I have a few questions for you.
Yes, of course.
Do you happen to know anything
about the Passenger Ship Spy Case
from ten years ago?
That's the first I'm hearing of it.
A spy came down here?
Then...
what about this?
The case where your former boss,
Hwang Hwa-san
murdered Kwon Soon-bok.
Well, now. My memory's
a bit fuzzy on that.
Didn't you take over the Hwasan Sect
and establish the Ingu Sect after that?
Oh, I didn't take it over.
I branched off on my own.
And I don't know what these were about
but what a tragedy.
I don't really follow the news,
so I don't know much
so I'm not sure how helpful
my answers can be.
Shall we continue, though?
Then I'll just ask you one last thing.
You know who this is, right?
Well, he's...
Isn't he the one running for mayor?
You don't watch the news, but you seem to
know Han Gyeong-wook quite well.
I've just seen his campaign posters
a few times.
Let's be honest.
These previous cases
and Han Gyeong-wook...
You know all about them, don't you?
What, are you interrogating me now?
Interrogating you? Me?
I'm just asking you questions.
Right, okay.
In any case, as for the details...
I'll hear them when I visit Han
Gyeong-wook in person.
Wait, you're going to visit him in person?
Oh, why?
I mean, it's not like you know him.
- So it shouldn't be a problem, right?
- Right. It's no problem.
I see.
Okay, got it.
Well, thank you so much
for your cooperation.
- Of course.
- Yes.
Still, if by any chance...
you remember anything...
IMCHEON DISTRICT PROSECUTORS' OFFICE
PROSECUTOR GANG YEONG-AE
- Please give me a call.
- Sure.
- Well, I'll be on my way.
- Yes, take care.
- Goodbye.
- Bye.
"He's a stranger."
What a joke.
IMCHEON DISTRICT PROSECUTORS' OFFICE
PROSECUTOR GANG YEONG-AE
Boss.
Is she really a prosecutor?
Why the hell is a prosecutor
showing up now, of all times?
Hey, this is no time
to be standing around.
- Have her tailed and report back to me.
- Yes, sir.
TWO UNREAD MESSAGES
OFFICER PARK MI-KYUNG
SEE YOU TOMORROW THEN!
YOUR BOOKING IS COMPLETE
A BETTER TOMORROW
A prosecutor from the Criminal Division
came to see him?
Yes.
I mean, everything the Ingu Sect
has ever done
she just threw it all in the boss's face.
As if she already knew everything.
And on top of that, the real kicker was...
she kept pressing him asking if he was
connected to Chief Han.
- Who? Chief Han?
- Yes.
He was already worried
about Heaven Capital
and terrified that
Chief Han would find out.
And then a prosecutor
shows up out of the blue.
In-gu is pretty much
losing his mind right now.
He's so cornered
he's ready to snap at
anyone who gets near him.
Damn.
This President Yoo is becoming
more and more of a problem.
So, is President Yoo
just going to stand by
and do nothing about that prosecutor?
Come on, no matter how reckless the boss
gets
you don't think he'd actually do
something to a prosecutor?
I mean, you mess with one
and your life is over in a flash.
Right?
Mess with a prosecutor
and you're completely screwed.
Yo!
What the hell are you doing here
so early in the morning?
There was something
I needed to check on urgently.
It looks like a critical problem has come
up with Heaven Capital.
- What's this punk up to now?
- A prosecutor...
paid a visit.
Looks like she got a whiff of what the
Ingu Sect's been doing
and came sniffing around.
How the hell would you know that?
Because she came to me
and asked a bunch of questions.
I played dumb
and said I didn't know anything
but it was a tough spot to be in.
I mean, now that a prosecutor's involved
I can't just let this slide
without reporting
such a serious matter to Chief Han.
You son of a bitch,
are you going to snitch to Chief Han?
What did you just call me?
Hey.
Yoo In-gu.
You think I'm a pushover
just because I'm being nice?
Do you?
How dare you threaten me?
Do you still not get it?
What are you talking about?
A prosecutor showed up! A prosecutor.
Don't you know what that means?
If she starts poking around Yeongseon
Island and blows our operation
do you think Chief Han, with his temper,
will just stand by and watch?
You, who caused this mess,
and me, who looked the other way...
we'll both be killed without a trace.
Got it?
No, no.
What was I thinking?
Look, I'm sorry for getting angry.
This is not good.
Before I get dragged down into this mess
I think the right thing to do
is report this to Chief Han.
- Chairman Do...
- Let go of me! Don't touch me.
I didn't touch you!
Come on, don't be like this.
That prosecutor...
I'll take care of her.
Just give me some time.
What are you going to do if I give you
time? That's ridiculous.
I have a way! I have a plan.
I do.
You said you trusted my abilities,
didn't you? Huh?
You said we're in the same boat.
Just give me some time,
and I'll handle it myself. I swear.
Jesus Christ.
You have one day.
If you can't fix this by tomorrow
then there's really nothing
I can do for you. Okay?
- One day?
- One day. Yeah?
Mr. Yoo. Don't keep...
- making me be the bad guy. All right?
- Okay.
- By tomorrow.
- Yeah, I got it.
CLOSED FOR DINNER TONIGHT
Ji-woo, what's this one's name?
- Masked Racer.
- Oh, Masked Racer.
Okay, then what about this guy?
A monster.
Gosh, you're a sharp judge of character.
Mom.
O-ran, you look amazing!
Well, she takes after me
so of course she's a knockout.
You know it.
Mom, you look really pretty today.
I just put on what I usually wear.
Should I change if it's too much?
No, it looks great on you.
After the play
let's go eat somewhere nice.
I've already found a place.
Let's go.
- Ji-woo, let's go.
- Okay, have fun, sweetie.
Let's go!
- We'll get going.
- All right.
- Have fun.
- We're off!
IMCHEON DISTRICT PROSECUTORS' OFFICE
PROSECUTOR GANG YEONG-AE
- Hello?
- Prosecutor Gang Yeong-ae.
Yes, speaking. Who is this?
I used to serve Chairman Hwang Hwa-san.
My name is Gang Beom-ryong.
I was told you'd clear
our chairman's name.
As much as I can
I want to help you with that.
Why should I...
trust you, Mr. Gang Beom-ryong?
Ten years ago...
The Passenger Ship Spy Case.
I was on that passenger ship.
I know all the details of the case
you're interested in.
You really know everything?
I'd like to meet you
in person to tell you.
Where are you right now, by any chance?
- On Yeongseon Island.
- Yeongseon Island?
Wait, Yoo In-gu...
Have you already met Yoo In-gu?
Yes, but it wasn't very fruitful.
Let's meet somewhere quiet.
I'll decide on the place.
HAN GYEONG-WOOK! THE EXPERT FOR IMCHEON'S
CULTURE AND INDUSTRY
- What brings you here?
- Well...
I was hoping I could borrow some money.
- Have a seat.
- Oh, okay.
IOU LOAN AMOUNT 50,000 WON
- Sir.
- Yes?
- You wrote this part wrong.
- No, I didn't write it wrong.
- No, I'm telling you, this is wrong.
- Fifty thousand won?
- Yes, fifty thousand won.
Fifty thousand won?
Yes, fifty thousand won.
I'm on a roll right now, sir.
So if I just pull the lever now,
I'll hit the jackpot.
- Get out.
- No, sir.
- I said, get out.
- No. I really need this. I...
- Hey, guys! Hey!
- Jackpot.
- Hey, get him out of here! Now!
- I'm about to hit the jackpot!
I swear, my time has come!
- Are you kidding me? Damn.
- No, I...
Hey.
- Just 50,000 won.
- Knock some sense into him. Seriously.
Just 50,000 won. I'm telling you.
I'm on a roll! Just 50,000 won!
Boss.
What should we do?
Where's the prosecutor?
She's snooping around Yeongseon Island
digging into Heaven Capital.
Boss, you shouldn't.
Let's postpone
the drug deal.
Do you have any idea how hard it was to
get this supplier?
I put all of the Ingu Sect's
money into this.
If this deal falls through,
we're bankrupt.
But what if...
What if that prosecutor bitch
gets a whiff of the drugs?
What if things go wrong
and Chief Han finds out?
This is on a whole different level
than the Martial Arts Master problem.
There's no going back from this, Boss.
Either way...
If the deal falls through,
the Chinese won't let it slide.
And if we don't deal
with the prosecutor by today
that fox Chairman Do
will tattle to Chief Han.
Whether we die because the deal is off,
or at the hands of Chief Han
we die either way.
Jeez, then what do we do?
No matter how I think about it
there's only one way to survive.
The prosecutor...
- Let's take her out.
- What?
Boss.
Going after a prosecutor
will blow this whole thing up.
We can dump her in the ocean
without a soul knowing.
We can bribe the Yeongseon Island cops
to erase any trace.
- But still...
- If the prosecutor disappears
everything's clean.
We can deal with
the Martial Arts Master after that.
Damn it.
Kang-sik, you stop yapping
and get some of your best guys ready.
When the time is right, we'll do the job.
Damn it, I knew this was going
to cause trouble.
RESTRICTED NUMBER
HILLSIDE CAFE
Yes. I've arrived.
She just went into
the Hillside Cafe in Nakwon-ri.
Hill... Hillside Cafe?
Hillside Cafe.
HILLSIDE CAFE
Twenty minutes.
Answer the phone.
This is driving me crazy.
Why isn't she answering?
Answer the phone... Damn it.
The number you have dialed is unavailable.
Please leave a message...
This is driving me crazy.
Taxi!
Hey!
Oh, look. We're next.
MASKED RACER
Hey, want to take one with Mom?
Come on, what is with you?
Ji-woo, what pose should we do?
I'll, um... I'll do this.
All right, let's go.
Hey, I'm gonna run to the restroom.
- Okay, go ahead.
- I'll be back.
Let's go, Ji-woo.
MASKED RACER
Ready to strike a pose, buddy?
- Like this?
- Wow, you're a natural.
Okay, one, two, three.
RESTRICTED NUMBER
Want to take one more, buddy?
Sorry about that. I messed up the shot.
Why are you calling?
And from a regular phone?
Ho-myeong, it's an emergency.
Get over here now.
What are you talking about?
Damn it, I can't.
I'm with my family at a show.
Listen, Yoo In-gu's crew
is going to take out Prosecutor Gang.
What did you say?
- Where are you right now?
- I'm on Yeongseon Island.
Prosecutor Gang
is on Yeongseon Island now?
Yeah.
Prosecutor Gang...
provoked Yoo In-gu,
and now that crazy bastard...
Look, I don't have time to explain.
Just get over here. Hurry!
This is driving me crazy, damn it.
If you don't come,
Prosecutor Gang is going to die, man.
But what's wrong with your voice?
It's nothing. I'm fine.
I'm just a little hurt. Now, hurry up.
If Prosecutor Gang goes down,
it's all over.
Ho-myeong, get here fast.
All right. I'll call you back.
Dad.
Do you have to go save the day?
Masked Racer always has to...
leave right when he's having fun.
But you're going off
to fight the bad guys.
So I'm okay.
Ji-woo.
The show will be starting shortly.
It's starting. Let's go.
We ask all audience members
to please enter the theater.
Hey, listen.
Well...
About the show...
Do you...
Do you think
- you could watch without me for a bit?
- What?
- What are you talking about?
- It's just...
something urgent came up.
I have to go take care of it.
What is it? Did the shop catch on fire?
What could be so urgent?
I'll explain when I get back.
I'm sorry. It's a real emergency.
So you can't even tell me what it is
but you have to leave for this emergency?
Mom.
I'm okay if we just watch it together.
Go save the day!
- I can't believe you.
- Mom, the show's starting.
Let's go watch.
Dad, go on.
I'm going to go watch the show with Mom.
Ji-woo, let me just
talk to your dad for a second.
I'm so sorry.
O-ran. Ji-woo.
I'll be back...
really soon.
Hey, wait.
Mom.
Wait...
HILLSIDE CAFE
Excuse me.
What happened here?
Don't even ask.
A while ago
some thugs stormed in here
trying to get a woman.
They totally wrecked the place.
Damn it.
Where did they all go?
I don't know.
They just sped off in a car.
Which way did they go?
They headed toward the main road.
Thank you.
SPECIAL THANKS TO OUR GUEST STARS
KIM SANG-KYUNG, KWON YUL, AND PARK JI-HWAN
Let's go together.
Han Gyeong-wook
and Yoo In-gu are connected.
They crashed into the Yeongseon River.
Are they dead?
If they're lucky,
they might have survived.
- Excuse me.
- I've got a bad feeling about this.
- Is he a criminal?
- You said you're Bong Je-sun, right?
The poor sap who lost
your home and got fired.
Have you been spying
on Jeong Ho-myeong lately?
What on earth are you hiding from me?
- Sir, are you sure nothing's wrong?
- I got kicked out.
How about we bring in a new member?
- I'll do my best.
- I'll give it a shot.
That's complete nonsense.
As an agent
for the National Intelligence Service
how could you team up with a thug?